字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
在我打败极速并拯救了多元宇宙后
After defeating Zoom and saving the multiverse,
我跑回到了过去
I ran back in time
创造出了另一条时间线  闪点
and created the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
我恢复了时间线原来的状态
I restored the timeline to how it was,
但发现有些事却不一样了
only to find things weren't as I left them.
我给我们的世界带来了新的威胁
I brought new threats to our world,
而我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
and I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我就是  闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
那是什么
What is that?
又一具表皮外壳
Another epidermal husk,
一具完整的人皮
a fully-intact human pelt.
关于成因我们目前有什么推测吗
Do we have any theories as to what's causing them?
-我是炼金术师  -你想做什么
- I am Alchemy. - Well, what do you want?
帮助人们发掘他们真正的潜力
To help people achieve their true potential.
我知道你很渴望能力
I know you want this more than anything,
但你要接受现实  这可能不会成真
but you have to face the fact that it might not happen.
整个多元宇宙里有这么多哈里森·威尔斯
There's a whole multiverse of Harrison Wells out there.
-你可以叫我HR  -你是冒牌的
- Call me HR. - You're a fake.
让我证明自己的价值
Let me prove my worth.
如果失败了  我就灰溜溜地回去自己的地球
If I fail, I will right back to my Earth.
但如果成功了
If I succeed,
我就在自己的生命中做了善举
I will have done some good with my life.
凯特琳  你所拥有的的能力
Caitlin, these powers you have,
你使用的越频繁
the more you use them,
就越难逆转到之前的状态
the more difficult they're going to be to reverse.
我很快
I'm fast,
相当快
really fast.
我甚至可能是现今世上速度最快的人
I might even be the fastest man alive.
当我跑起来的时候
And when I'm running,
我觉得这是世间无与伦比的感受
there's no greater feeling in the world.
我在城市中来回穿梭  如同守护天使
I can move through the city like a guardian angel,
保护那些需要保护的人
protecting people who need me.
你得慢点
You gotta slow down.
看着路  好吧
And watch where you're going, okay?
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
不过滑板很酷
Cool skateboard, though.
谢谢
Thanks.
他们甚至给我起了个名字
They even have a name for me.
他们叫我"闪电小子"
They call me "Kid Flash."
闪电小子
Kid Flash?
是的  虽然这名字需要改改  但是老爸
Yeah, the name needs some work, but, Dad,
我跟你说  这感觉很真实
I'm telling you, it all just felt so real
就像是真实发生的一样
like it was actually happening.
你经常做这种梦吗
And how often are you getting these dreams?
过去几天一直做
Last couple nights.
过去几天
Last couple?
沃利  这正是
Wally, this is exactly
发生在弗朗奇·凯恩身上的情况
what Frankie Kane said happened to her.
她做了一些梦  很多痛苦的梦
She had dreams, a lot of painful ones,
然后她就听到脑子里有炼金术师的声音
and then she started hearing Alchemy's voice in her head
后来她就变成了磁红女
until she became Magenta.
我跟她是两码事  老爸
This is totally different, Dad.
不  不是的
No. No, it's not.
是  就是
Yes, it is.
我在梦里是极速者
I'm a speedster in my dreams.
我不是邪恶的人格分裂患者
I'm not an evil split personality.
我是在帮助大家  不是伤害他们
I'm helping people, not hurting them.
老爸  这可能意味着
Dad, this could mean that
我的能力终于要显现出来了
my powers are finally manifesting.
不  我觉得现在你和那些最后死掉或者
No, I think this means that you have a lot in common
进监狱的人有很多相似之处
right now with people who either ended up in prison or dead.
只不过我被粒子加速器爆炸
Except for the fact that I got hit by the dark matter
释放出的暗物质击中过
from the particle accelerator explosion,
就像杰西一样
just like Jesse.
我去上课了
I'm going to class.
朱利安  需要我先给你准备好
Hey, Julian, do you want me to get started
DNA分析报告吗
on the DNA analysis for you?
我要你做那个干嘛
Why would I need you to do that?
我不知道  我就是觉得
I don't know, I just figured
我们上次合作得很好
we worked so well together last time.
怎么  好到我还想再来一次吗
What, that I'd want to do it again?
我们一起办了个案子  喝了杯酒
One shared case and one shared drink
并不代表我们就是好哥们了  好吧
does not make us mates, okay?
霍尔顿女士
Miss Horton.
艾伦先生
Mr. Allen.
-阿尔伯特先生  -早上好
- Mr. Albert. - Morning.
又来一个
New one?
是的  六号
Yeah, number six.
昨晚发现的
Found it last night.
那这应该算是好消息了
Well, this should come as a welcome surprise.
你现在是超能力者
You've been reassigned to meta-human
犯罪现场调查组的全职人员了
crime scene investigation full-time.
全职
Full-time?
我们现在把所有的力量
We're pouring all the resources we can
都投入到这个"外壳"案子上了
into figuring out this husk problem,
尤其是因为上一个外壳是
especially considering the last one turned out to be
那个邪恶极速者  竞争者
that evil speedster, The Rival.
有什么问题  担心
Any questions, concerns,
你们就去找汉克森法官  好吧
you guys direct them to Judge Hankerson, yeah?
-好的  -谢谢
- All right. - Thank you.
乔
Joe.
塞西尔
Cecile.
我都不知道你要来
I didn't know you were gonna be over here.
只要有借口能来见你  我都会把握住
Any excuse I have to run into you, I take it.
我很期待明天晚上
You know, I'm really looking forward to tomorrow night.
我也是
So am I.
-是吗  -是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
太好了  那我就
Okay, good, then I,
-到时见了  -好的
- I'll see you then. - All right.
是我想的那样吗
Yo. Is that what I think it was?
你邀请她来跟我们一起看电影了吗
You asked her to movie night with us?
太棒了  你什么时候做的
That's awesome. When did you do that?
怎么做到的
How'd you do it?
虽然我现在很想像年轻人那样
As much as I'd like to gossip with you
跟你八卦一下
like a teenager right now,
但是我们有另外一件事要说
there's something else we need to talk about.
什么事
What?
沃利
Wally.
他一直在做梦
He's been having dreams.
做梦
Dreams?
梦到救人于水火
Saving people,
成为极速者
becoming a speedster.
他称自己为闪电小子
He called himself Kid Flash.
闪电小子  他特别说了这个名字吗
Kid Flash, he-- he said that name, specifically?
他有麻烦了  是吗
He's in trouble, isn't he?
如果他在做成为闪电小子的梦
If Wally's having dreams of being Kid Flash,
那他就有麻烦
then he's in trouble,
但是别担心  我们会想到办法的
yeah, but don't worry, okay, we'll figure it out.
-回头见  -好
- I'll see you later. - All right.
闪电侠
第三季
第六集
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
是啊  他竟然还没走
Yeah, we do. He's still here.
西斯科  显而易见的玩笑
Cisco, comedy of the obvious.
我承诺要在你们地球上证明我的用处
I made a pact to justify my presence on your Earth
我想我找到了
and I think I got something.
-我们洗耳恭听  -好
- We're all ears. - Okay.
我看了能找到的每一篇新闻报道
I read every news report I can get my hands on.
然后我得出了结论
And I have come to the conclusion
你们这个组织
that this very operation
就是个定时炸弹
is a ticking time-bomb.
这话什么意思
What do you mean?
你不能把所有时间都放在
You can't spend all your time working on--
放在这上面  不管这是什么东西
working on whatever-- whatever this is.
这是一套非常精密的
This-- this is a very delicate
能力抑制手铐
set of power-dampening cuffs.
我们需要用它来阻止超能力者的
We need them to stop the meta-humans.
正是我的意思
My point exactly.
用不了多久
It's not gonna be long
人们就会开始把事情联系在一起
before people start putting the pieces together
发现你们在这里做的事
and figure out what you're doing here.
你们在和闪电侠合作
You're working with The Flash.
好吧  那你有什么想法
Okay, so what's your idea?
完美的伪装
The perfect disguise.
我们重开这间实验室
We reopen this laboratory
我变成了新尖端科研实验室的代言人
and I become the face of the new S.T.A.R. Labs
新尖端科
研实验室
博物馆
过去的价值
以及对未来的承诺
博物馆
Museum.
这里只有一个问题
There's only one problem with that.
就是你的脸
It's your face.
在这一带里你算是众所周知的谋杀犯
You're kind of a known murderer around these parts.
那个邪恶的威尔斯
You see, the evil Wells,
别把他和混蛋但不邪恶的威尔斯混淆
not to be confused with the dick-ish but not evil Wells,
他承认谋杀了巴里的母亲
he confessed to killing Barry's mother.
所以基本来说  如果你走出这间实验室
So basically, if you step foot outside this lab,
你就会被逮捕
you'll be arrested.
什么  现在才告诉我  你们两个坏蛋
What-- you're just telling me this now, you two rascals?
那暗码算法呢  那留言呢
What about the cryptogram? What about the message?
来到这个地球上  重新开始
Come to this Earth. Get a fresh start.
你的简历上还写着
Well, what about your résumé
自己是个世界知名的天才科学家
as a world-renowned genius scientist?
说得也是  看来我们扯平了
That's a good point. I guess we're even.
如果绳子打了结  有耐心才能解开
If a string is in a knot, patience will untie it.
有耐心可以做很多事  你有尝试过吗
Patience can do lots of things. Have you ever tried it?
在我遇到问题时  我亲爱的妈妈
My dear ma used to say that to me all the time
都会和我说这句话
any time I had a problem.
现在我有麻烦了
Now I have a problem.
看来我要用这句格言来想出办法
I guess I'm gonna use that adage to figure it out.
新尖端科研实验室博物馆  好好考虑一下
S.T.A.R. Labs Museum, think about it.
你认为地球十九上的人会想念盒子里的蜡笔
You think everyone on Earth-19 is missing crayons in the box,
还是想念他呢
or just him?
呼叫斯诺博士
Paging Dr. Snow.
-你神游了  -抱歉
- You are out of it. - Sorry.
这和你最近悄悄去找你妈妈有关吗？
This have anything to do with your recent visit with Mom?
我只是  最近睡眠不好
I just-- I haven't been sleeping well,
但我没事
but I'm okay.
喝咖啡吗
Coffee?
太好了
Perfect.
这么说我的确有过超能力吗
So I did have powers?
我做过闪电小子
I was Kid Flash?
在闪点里  是的
In Flashpoint, yes.
我就知道是这么回事
I knew that this was happening.
你之前为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me before?
因为
Because...
因为什么
Because why?
好吧  沃利
All right, fine, Wally, it, look--
在那条时间线上
in that timeline,
你在对抗竞争者
you were fighting The Rival.
爱德华·克拉里斯
Edward Clariss?
爱德华·克拉里斯  是的
Edward Clariss, yeah.
你没能阻止他
You couldn't stop him.
那里没有尖端科研实验室
There was no S.T.A.R. Labs.
没有团队帮你
There was no team to help you.
只有你和爱瑞丝
It was just you and Iris.
你们俩是打击罪犯的
The two of you were a brother-sister
姐弟超级英雄小队
superhero crime-fighting team.
你之前怎么没告诉我们
Why didn't you tell us this before?
你之前不想知道你在闪点里的生活
You didn't want to know about your Flashpoint lives.
但是听我说
But look, listen to me,
你受伤了
you got hurt, all right?
伤得很严重
You got hurt bad.
那又怎样
So what?
那是闪点里的我  又不是这里的我
That's that me, it's not this me.
而且我想成为极速者
And I want to be a speedster.
我想成为闪电侠
I-- I want to be a flash.
不不  你不想
No, no, no, you don't.
我想
Yes, I do.
你没理解他说的话
You're not hearing what he's saying.
他在告诉我们那样很危险
He's telling us it's not safe.
谁管巴里说什么
Who cares what Barry's saying?
我们怎么知道他说的是不是真话
How do we even know he's telling the truth?
沃利  别这样  这不是因为
Wally, come on, this isn't because of
粒子加速器  而是因为炼金术师
the particle accelerator, it's because of Dr. Alchemy.
和发生在弗朗奇·凯恩身上的事是一样的
It's the same thing that happened to Frankie Kane.
-你们根本不知道  -我们知道
- You don't know that. - Yes, we do.
我们需要阻止这种事发生
And we need to try to keep it from happening.
为什么不直接说这到底怎么回事
Why don't we just say what this is really about?
你不介意巴里拥有超能力
You're okay with Barry having powers;
你不介意巴里直面危险
you're okay with Barry running into danger,
与所有超能力者战斗
fighting all these metas.
他搞砸多少次都没关系
He can screw up over and over again
你都不介意  因为他是巴里
You're okay with all of it because he's Barry.
但你不给我同样的空间
But you won't give me the same amount of leeway
因为最终说来
because at the end of the day,
你就是不相信我
you just don't trust me.
你知道不是这样的  沃利
You know that's not true, Wally.
我不需要你帮我爸爸挡下这个问题
I don't need you fighting my dad's battles for him.
说吧  乔
Say it, Joe.
你不相信我  是不是
You don't trust me, do you?
沃利
Wally...
看来我想得没错
That's what I thought.
不  你没懂我的意思
No. No, you're not listening to me.
我说了股票贬值了
I said the shares are undervalued
股票如果下跌  你应该多买不是少买
so if the stock drops, you should buy more, not less.
不  不是那么回事
No, that-that's not how it works.
看看资产负债表吧
Look, just look at its balance sheet.
如果你现在出售  会损失一大笔钱
If you sell now, you're going to lose a lot of money.
我明白
I understand that.
当然那是你的钱
Of course it's your money.
等一等就是了
Just hold onto it then.
你知道吗  如果你不打算听...
You know what? If you're not gonna listen...
眼周有瘀点  喉头破碎
Petechiae around the eye, the crushed larynx.
这可怜的家伙
This poor chap has got
脖子上全是指纹
fingerprints all round his neck.
他显然是被掐死的
He's clearly been strangled.
我听到很多目击者说
I heard multiple witnesses
这人被一团阴影攻击
said the man was attacked by a shadow.
所以一个超能力者从永无乡
So a meta from Neverland's made the trip
来到中城了  真棒
to Central City. Fabulous.
目前没有法医证据表明
So far there's no forensic evidence
这是一起袭击事件
that there was an assailant.
没有撕裂伤口  没有指甲印记
No laceration marks. No fingernail marks.
指甲下都没有DNA证据吗
No DNA evidence underneath the fingernails even?
还没有  我们得等等看
Nothing yet, we'll have to wait and see.
总会有什么的
There's always something.
装好尸体  我们回实验室见
Bag the body up and I'll meet you back at the lab.
好  再见
Yeah. See ya.
还有  朱利安
Oh, and Julian, um,
我要去看公园看个电影
I'm going to that movie in the park thing
跟乔和他的...还有我的爱瑞丝和一些朋友
with Joe and his--or my-Iris and some other friends.
如果你想来  八点开始
If you felt like going, it starts at 8:00.
我们都是一群书呆子  所以
We're all a bunch of nerds, so
你肯定融得进来
you'll fit right in.
这个提议很诱人  艾伦
Well, that's a very enticing offer, Allen,
但我今晚其实要去见女朋友  所以
but I'm actually seeing my girlfriend tonight, so.
你有女友了  我都不知道
Oh, you have a girlfriend? I didn't know that.
我肯定还有很多事是你不知道的
I'm sure there's lots about me that you don't know.
-再会  -好
- Cheerio. - Yeah.
-艾伯特  -警探
- Albert. - Detective.
有发现吗
Anything?
至少现在还没发现
With the--uh, nothing yet, at least.
你今天上午看到沃利了吗
Have you seen Wally this morning?
没有  怎么了
No. Why?
他一气之下离开了家
He left the house in a huff.
他不接我电话了
He won't answer my calls.
爱瑞丝现在正在找他呢
Iris is out there looking for him right now.
你想让我在全城找找他吗
Did you want me to run around the city?
也许等我联系不上他再说
Maybe if I can't get ahold of him.
沃利有些地方说对了
What Wally said, it's partially true.
我没有回答他的问题是因为
I didn't answer his question because
我不像信任你的超能力那样
I--I don't trust him with these powers
信任他的超能力
the same way I trust you with them.
你得和他谈一谈这事
You got to talk to him about that.
告诉他为什么  尤其是现在
You know, tell him why, especially now.
我会的  但得先找到他
I will, I mean, just gotta find him first.
我会一直打电话给他
Look, I'll just keep calling him.
他总有一下会接的吧
He's got to answer at some point, right?
我也感觉很抱歉
Man, I feel bad, too.
这是你与塞西尔的第一次约会
It's your first date with Cecile
而你还需要担心这种事
and you got to worry about this.
别担心那个
Don't worry about that.
那是我生活中能控制住的一部分
That's one part of my life I can control.
怎么了
Yes?
你见到HR了吗
Have you seen HR?
也许他在他的房间里冥思呢
Maybe he's meditating in his room.
不  他不在那里
No, he's not there.
HR  极速实验室需要你  速来
HR, you're needed in the Speed Lab, now.
他可能在通风口做反向拉伸呢
He could be doing inversion stretches in the intake.
你也看到了啊
You saw that too, huh?
HR  他不在那
HR! He's not there.
可能在煮另一壶咖啡呢
Probably just brewing another pot of coffee.
-他就只喝那个  -也不是
- It's all he drinks. - Not that either.
好吧  你为什么这么想找他
Okay. Why do you need him so badly?
他在查看我的东西  但是现在
He's going through my stuff, but now...
他开始胡乱搞了
He's just being stupid about it.
胡乱搞什么
Stupid about what?
天  我发誓我修好了安全系统的
God, I swear I fixed the security system.
你这家伙是谁
Who the hell are you?
HR
HR.
抱歉
Apologies.
HR
HR.
看  你刚才见到的是
See? Ah. What you've just been witness to
我搭档兰道夫·摩根的模样
was my partner's likeness, Randolf Morgan.
好吧  我知道怎么回事了
Okay, I see what's going on here.
你们这个地球上没有
You don't have facial transmogrification
面部变形技术  对吧
on this planet, do you?
不  我们显然没有
No, we certainly do not.
那好吧
Well then,
还好在被我遗忘的背包里
it's a good thing for me I found this little contraption
找到了这个小装置
in my satchel-forgot I brought it.
简直太好玩了
It's so fun.
好玩  这是什么原理
So fun? How does this work?
光线折射技术
Light refraction technology.
光线折射
Light refraction?
我想...我不...兰道夫
I think--I don't-- Randolf,
我的工作搭档
my--business partner,
他对科技更在行
he's sort of more with the science.
但这小管子在解决哈里森·威尔斯
But this little sucker is gonna go a long way
易容难题上帮了我大忙
to solving my Harrison Wells facial issues.
在找回我的超能力手铐前这个归我管
I'm gonna hang onto this until I get my power cuffs back.
什么  你的超能力手铐
What, your power cuffs?
你的超能力者能力抑制手铐吗
Your meta-human power-dampening cuffs?
正是那些突然失踪的手铐
Those very ones, the ones that are missing all of a sudden.
你觉得是我拿走了吗
What--you think-- you think I took them?
我没有拿  我拿手铐做什么
I didn't take them. What do I need cuffs for?
我才刚来到这个地球  孤身一人
I just got to this Earth. I came alone.
我还谁都没见过  就算我见过了
I haven't met anyone yet; it's gonna take a while,
也得等一阵才能用上手铐
even when I do meet them, to get to the cuff stage.
大伙们
Hey, guys?
到表层控制室来
Guys, I need you in the Cortex.
被阴影杀害  这可新鲜了
Killed by a shadow? That's a new one.
中城记录
也许就是这杀了爱德华·克拉里斯
Maybe that's what killed Edward Clariss.
克拉里斯是超能力者
Clariss was a meta-human.
这个受害者看起来不像
This victim doesn't appear to be.
知不知道这个阴影超能力者是受
Do we know if this shadow meta is from the
粒子加速器爆炸还是炼金术博士的影响
particle accelerator explosion or from Dr. Alchemy?
还不知道
Not yet, no.
其实我们还没找到证据以便分析
We actually haven't found any evidence to process.
弗朗西斯科  如果我们有办法
If only we had a way, Francisco,
看到事件经过就好了
to see what happened.
犯罪现场在哪里
Where was the crime scene located?
在查伯克  帕尔默街和雷辛街交口
In Chubbuck, uh, Palmer and Racine,
昨晚11点左右
around 11 last night.
这会让我做噩梦的
That's gonna give me night terrors.
-阴影  -什么
- Shade. - What?
我的地球上有一个
We had a meta-hominid on my planet
自称"阴影"的超能力者
who could do virtually the same thing,
差不多也能干这种事
called himself "Shade."
他做过什么  轻视敌人吗
What did he do, throw his side-eye at his enemies?
不清楚  这是个可怕的绰号  是不是
Few I know, it's a terrible nickname, right?
但阴影可以通过高频振动
But what Shade could do was vibrate at such a high frequency
制造出他是阴影的幻象
he created the illusion that he was a shadow.
我就是这么做的
That's how I phase.
你觉得他也在这么做吗
Do you think he's doing the same thing?
肯定是
He has to be.
热能信号处于波动之中
Heat signature's fluctuating.
红移轨迹很夸张
Red shift is ridiculous.
好  那么他是
Okay, so he is.
他肯定是在攻击时让自己的分子降速
He must be slowing down his molecules whenever he attacks.
我们只要想办法让他的分子一直降速
So we just have to figure out a way to keep them slowed down,
就可以抓到他了
and that should be enough to grab him.
好  可以开始了吗
All right, can you get started?
可以  但现在就开始吗
Okay, but, like, right this minute?
是的  抱歉  我们得...
Yeah, I'm sor--we just--
得迅速解决掉他好专心对付炼金术师
we gotta stop this guy fast so we can focus on Alchemy.
沃利最近梦见
Wally has been having
自己成极速者
dreams about being a speedster,
炼金术师的梦境
Alchemy dreams.
他在闪点中是极速者吗
He was a speedster in Flashpoint?
我们还该知道谁会有超能力吗
Anyone else gonna have powers we should know about?
没了
No.
好的  开始研究阴影吧
All right. I'm gonna work on Shade.
-我来监督  -你去找我的手铐
- I'll supervise. - You're gonna find my cuffs.
我得去找手铐了
I'll have to find some cuffs.
我得回去工作
All right, I got to get back to work
以防朱利安抓狂
before Julian loses his mind.
中城警局
沃利  爸爸又打来了
Wally, it's your dad, again.
回我电话  好吗
Just give me a call back, all right?
短信也行  让我知道你没事就行
Or a text, I just need to know you're okay.
我没事
I'm okay.
沃利
Wally.
你不能这样
You can't do that.
不能就这么玩消失
You can't just disappear.
我只想让你知道
I just wanted to let you know
我没事  那么
I'm fine, so.
过来
Come here.
听我说  你是对的
Listen, you were right.
我确实区别对待你和巴里
I do treat Barry differently than I treat you.
但不是因为我觉得巴里比你优秀
But not because I think Barry's better than you.
那为什么
Then why?
沃利  你和我小时候很像
Wally, you're a lot like I was as a kid.
你无所畏惧  勇于冒险
You're fearless and you take risks
会让你像我之前一样惹很多麻烦
and that makes you a handful just like I was.
现在你要获得超能力了
And now you're getting powers.
这种孤立感会让我紧张
That alone would make me nervous
因为我知道如果我有超能力了会怎么做
because I know what I would have done if I got powers.
但是你获得速度的方式
But you're not getting your speed
跟巴里的不同
the same way Barry got his.
你获得速度的方式将会和
You're getting your speed the way
磁红女和竞争者一样
Magenta and The Rival got theirs.
所以不是我不信任你  沃利  只是
So it's not that I don't trust you, Wally, it's just
我不信现在在你身上发生的事
I don't trust what's going on with you right now.
这把我吓坏了
And that scares the living hell out of me.
我明白  爸爸
I know, Dad.
我懂
I get it.
好  那么
Okay, so
我们去尖端科研实验室
let's get you to S.T.A.R. Labs
-看看能做些什么  -好的
- and see what we can do. - All right.
华莱士
Wallace.
华莱士·韦斯特
Wallace West.
沃利
Wally.
Wally!
西斯科
Hey, Cisco.
干嘛
Yes?
我拿了你的手铐
I took your cuffs.
为什么
Why?
因为我需要它们
Because I need them.
这是什么大胆的
Is--is this some sort of, um,
时尚选择吗  因为你又不是超能力...
bold fashion choice 'cause you're not a meta-hu--hu--
者
human.
没想到吧
Surprise.
几个月前开始的
It started a few months ago.
所以你去找你妈妈
That's why you went to see your mom,
看她能不能帮你
to see if she could help you.
但她帮不了我
But she can't.
我什么测试都做了
I've run every test.
谁都帮不了我
There's nothing that anyone can do.
我要你帮忙
I need a favor.
我要你用震波看看我的未来
I need you to vibe me in the future
因为我要知道我会不会变成...
because I need to know if I become...
她
her.
你不会变成她的
You're not gonna become her.
好了  你有了这超能力
Okay, just because you have these powers
并不是说你会变成冰霜杀手
doesn't mean you're gonna turn into Killer Frost.
我觉得有可能
I think it might.
求你了
Please?
我只想确认一下
I just need to know for sure.
我得知道我会不会变坏
I need to know if I become evil
因为要是变坏了  我就得离开
because if I do, I have to leave
不再回来
and never come back.
怎么样
And?
我什么都没看到
I didn't see anything.
你没事
You're fine.
谢谢你  谢谢
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
还有拜托
Please, um,
先别跟其他人说这事  好吗
don't tell anyone about this yet, okay?
-没问题  -好
- Of course. - Okay.
这上面显示你的生命体征没问题  沃利
According to this, all your vitals are fine, Wally.
沃利  你看到了什么
Wally, what did you see?
我又变成闪电小子了
I was Kid Flash again,
但这次的梦不太好
but this time it wasn't a good dream.
我在一个废弃的锯木厂跟竞争者作战
I was fighting The Rival at some abandoned sawmill.
那是你受伤前在闪点发生的事
That's what happened in Flashpoint before you got hurt.
那些不只是梦
They're not just dreams,
肯定是那里生活的记忆
they must be memories of that life.
获得超能力的人越来越多了
More and more people are getting powers.
好  我们该怎么阻止
Okay, so how do we stop this?
我是说这还能阻止得了吗
I mean, is there any stopping it even?
如果炼金术师能在中城警局找到你
If Alchemy could reach you at CCPD,
那不管你在哪他都能找到你吧
he could probably reach you from anywhere, right?
我有个提议
I have a suggestion.
在找到解决办法前
Why don't we throw Wallace in the pipeline
不如把华莱士关到管道监狱
until we figure this situation out.
你要把他关起来
You want to lock him up?
对  我同意乔  把他关起来
Yeah, I agree with Joe, we lock him up
因为想想看
because think about this.
我们没法阻止炼金术师入侵华莱士的大脑
We can't stop Alchemy from getting into Wallace's head,
但把他关进管道监狱  到时我们就能
but we put him in the pipeline, then we control the situation
掌控局面了
from there on out.
虽然我不太乐意  爸爸
As much as I don't like it, Dad,
但他或许是对的
maybe he's not wrong.
等我们想到办法保你安全
But only till we figure out
就把你放出来
a better way to make you safe.
对  我同意乔
Yeah, I agree with Joe.
我去跟塞西尔说不去看电影了
I'm gonna cancel this movie with Cecile.
等等  你跟塞西尔有约吗
Wait, wait, you've got a date with Cecile?
对  我今晚本来
Yeah, I was gonna bring her
要带她去公园看电影的
to movie in the park tonight.
别爽约啊
Well, don't not go.
你把太多精力放在我们身上了
You've put your life on hold for us long enough.
对  爸爸  他说得对
Yeah, Dad, he's right, I mean,
去吧  乔·韦斯特  别只会当老爸
go be Joe West; you're always Dad.
我们会守着沃利  保证不出意外
Yeah, we'll stay with Wally, and make sure nothing happens.
我跟她说你们都会来
I told her all of you were coming with me.
难道就我一个人去吗
Am I gonna be the only one that shows up?
我想去看电影
I would love to see a movie.
-什么电影  -《闪灵》
- What movie is this? - "The Shining."
《闪灵》  我爱死这电影了
"The Shining," oh, I love that movie.
那电影把你吓惨了
That movie freaks you out.
你从不敢看格雷迪双胞胎那部分
You have never made it past the part with the Grady twins.
那个嘛  当时...
That's--that's-- that was--
我当时还小
I was younger.
那我陪你去看吧
Why don't I go with you?
你确定你不想留下...
You sure you don't want stay...
不  我想跟你一起
No, I want to be with you.
不管怎样  人越多越热闹
Either way, the more the merrier.
我们一起去吧
Let's do it.
这可是我小说的精彩素材
Hell, this will be great fodder for my novel.
慢着  你们没跟他说
Hold on, you guys didn't tell him about?
乔  不是
Joe, no.
他们跟我说了
They--they told me,
终于说了  这群小混蛋
finally, the little scamps.
但我想我已经找到
But I think that I've worked my way
这问题的解决办法了
around that little problem.
看着
Watch this.
看我的...
Let me just...
你做了什么
What--what did you do?
你刚用失忆棒闪我们了
Did you just neuralyze us?
不  只是调整了你们的视网膜
No, I gave you a simple retinal adjustment
这样你们都能看到我HR的样子
so all of you can see me, HR,
其他人看到的则是...
while the rest of the world sees...
兰多夫·摩根
Randolf Morgan.
乔  我保证我会很安静的
Joe, I promise, I'll be so--I'll be so quiet.
你甚至察觉不到我在那  默默观影
You won't even know I'm there. Silent observer.
好
All right.
沃利  有事通知我
Wally, keep me posted.
好  我不会有事的
Yeah, I'll be fine.
好好玩吧
Just go have fun.
太好了
That's great.
恐怖电影秀
霍福赫公园
好  我们想在后面三分之二
All right, we want to be 2/3 to the back,
-正中间的位置  -屏幕太小了
- right in the middle. - That's a very small screen.
都不知道能不能看到...
Like, I don't know if we're gonna be able to see from--
不  HR  屏幕刚刚好  懂吗
No, HR, the screen is perfect, okay?
-不会影响观影效果  -但我们离太远
- We'll be able to see fine. - But we're so far--
技师混音的时候
That's where the engineer sits
-就是坐在那里的  好吗  -好吧
- when he mixes the sound, all right? - All right.
电影《闪灵》的导演
你要想体会库布里克的体验  那...
When you want to get the Kubrick experience, that's...
-好吧  -那里就是最佳位置
- All right, yeah. - The sweet spot, right there.
不懂了  或许我们该坐近点  比如在
I don't know, maybe we get a little closer, like right by...
不如座位的事就交给我来操心吧
Why don't you let us worry about the seats?
你负责好零食和饮料就好
You take care of the snacks and the drinks.
主意不错
Great idea.
随时效劳
Any time.
我没...
Oh, I don't--
我很肯定他们
I'm pretty sure they're
不会接受我地球上的货币
not gonna take the money from my Earth.
-我觉得不会  -什么
- I don't think. - What?
-这是什么  -这是个赫尔币
- What is this? - That's a helbing.
你现在这么做
Here's what you're gonna do.
你去买我们要的东西
You're gonna get us what we need,
去吧  去那边的小摊买东西
you're gonna do that, go over to that stand over there.
-好主意  -你给我们买点
- Great idea. - You're gonna get us some
甘草棒糖  枣子
licorice sticks, some Jujubes.
甘草...  枣...
Licorice...Juju...
知道了  还有咖啡
Yeah, and coffee.
你需要什么
Do you want anything?
-不用了  谢谢  -好的
- No thanks. - Okay.
好了
Okay.
你没事吧  西斯科
You okay, Cisco?
没事  没事  你知道
Yeah. Yeah, you know,
就是应付HR
just trying to deal with HR.
自从你对我用过震波之后
Yeah, 'cause you've been on edge
就一直有点心神不宁
ever since you vibed me.
你能告诉我你看见什么了吗
Are you gonna tell me what you saw?
什么  我告诉过你我看见的东西了
What? I told you what I saw.
不是  说实话
No, but, for real.
我能看得出你没对我说实话
I can tell when you're not being honest with me.
我是她吗
Am I her?
是的
Yeah.
对  你就是她
Yeah, you're her.
我  我看见我们两个了
I--I saw the both of us
在打架
fighting.
就像火力全开的震波大战冰霜杀手
Like full-on Vibe versus Killer Frost.
我们就像是一对超能力友敌
It's like we're meta-frenemies.
那你用震波看过什么未来的事情
Well, have you ever vibed anything from the future
最后没有成为现实的吗
that didn't come true?
只有地球二粉碎这件事
Just Earth-2 being ripped to shreds.
但这不能说明不会再发生
But that doesn't mean that can't happen again.
凯特琳
Caitlin,
你得告诉他们
you have to tell them.
你必须得告诉大家
You have to tell the team.
我们必须得弄明白发生了什么
We have to figure out what's going on.
不  太迟了
No. It's too late.
你已经无能为力了
There's nothing you can do.
不需要有任何人知道
Nobody else needs to know.
我很久没看过电影
I haven't been to a movie in forever.
只要有时间我就会去  我是说
I come whenever I can, I mean,
这算是个和孩子们的夏日传统
sort of a summer tradition with the kids.
是吗
Yeah?
你知道  很搞笑  你不用把我定义为
You know, it's funny, you don't really peg me
喜欢看恐怖电影的人
for a, uh, horror movie type.
我觉得你可能更喜欢看言情片
I thought maybe you'd be more of a chick-flicky.
-你还真幽默  -是啊
- Oh, you got jokes. - Yeah.
如果你没有这么迷人我会生气的
I might be mad if you weren't so gorgeous.
迷人  真的吗
Gorgeous, really?
如果我很迷人  那你怎么
If I'm so gorgeous, then how come you're
一直在看手机呢
spending more time looking at that than you are at me?
你知道吗
You know what?
你说得对  塞西尔  很抱歉
You're right, Cecile, I'm sorry.
我儿子  沃利  他...
My son, Wally, he's...
正经历一些变故  我就是...
going through some changes and I'm just--
非常担心他
Just really concerned.
乔  我们可以下次再看电影
Joe, we can do this another time.
不不不不  我真的很想和你在一起  真的
No-no-no-no, I really want to be here with you, I do.
只是当我的孩子受伤了  我...
It's just that when one of my kids is hurting I'm...
我就完全不能考虑到其它事情
Can't think about anything else at all.
我完全理解
Completely understand.
-你有孩子了吗  -有
- You have kids? - Yeah.
是个女儿
Daughter.
刚满18岁
Just turned 18.
还有不到一年的时间她就要离开我去上大学了
I have less than a year before she leaves me for college.
天  你该带她来的
Oh, man, you should have brought her.
我把你从她身边抢走来看恐怖电影
I drag you away from her so you can watch a horror movie.
会这样做的男人还真不多
Not many men could.
我很高兴你最终搞清楚自己想要什么了
I'm just glad you finally figured out what you want.
我也是
Me too.
沃利  你没事吧
Wally, you okay?
我真的不想这么做
I hate that we have to do this.
他是如此想得到能力  现在我们把他关起来
He so badly wanted powers, and, now, to keep him locked up
让他得不到能力  这真是...
so he doesn't get them, it's...
挺残酷的  我知道
It's hard, I know.
我不知道你会不会这么做
I don't know if you actually do.
什么意思
What does that mean?
沃利一心想帮助人们
All Wally wants to do is to help people.
看着你每天做这些而他只能
And to see you do that every day while all he can do
站在一边旁观
is stand by and watch,
有时候做个旁观者很难
It's hard being a bystander sometimes.
你难道也有这样的感觉吗
You don't feel that way too, do you?
巴里...
Barry...
这样说吧
Come on.
我在这的贡献是有限的
My contributions here are limited.
我不了解科学
I don't know science.
我没有超能力
I don't have powers.
我不知道怎么帮助你
I don't know how to help you.
没有你我做不到这些
I couldn't do this without you.
不是那样的
That's not true.
真的
That is true.
不管你意识到没有  没有爱瑞丝·韦斯特
Whether you realize it or not, there is no Flash
就没有闪电侠
without Iris West.
我吃了好多这个
I'm wolfing this.
-听我说  这挺好吃的  -挺好吃的
- I'm telling you, it's so good. - It is good.
爆米花和电影有什么相关
What is it about popcorn and the movies?
你没事吧
Hey, you okay?
没事
Yeah, fine.
-你好  我是凯特琳  -你好
- Hi, I'm Caitlin. - Hi.
塞西尔  很高兴认识你
Cecile. Nice to meet you.
-你肯定就是西斯科了  -我就是
- And you must be Cisco. - That's me.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
别把我给忘了
Don't forget about me.
你好
Hello.
我是HR
I'm HR.
HR·兰道夫
HR Randolf.
见到你实在荣幸
It's amazing to meet you.
-够了  -实在荣幸
- All right, now. - Amazing.
然后她对我说
And so then-- then she says to me,
你是外国来的甜心
"Oh, so you are hot chocolate from another land."
我说  先别急
I said, "Okay, easy, now."
然后她说  等一下
Then she, "Wait a minute.
你会说外语吗
Do you speak a foreign language?"
你怎么回答的
What did you say?
我说  当然会
Well, I said, "Sure."
只要我知道那些"单词"
"As long as I know the words."
我想打人
I'm gonna smack somebody.
恐怖电影秀  霍福赫公园
公园电影放映
欢迎欣赏
中城电影协会
公园电影放映
大家快跑  快跑
Everybody, move, move!
是阴影
It's Shade.
他在霍福赫公园
He's at Hofherr Park.
华莱士
Wallace.
华莱士·韦斯特
Wallace West.
是时候
The time has come
拿回你被夺去的了
to restore what was taken from you.
是时候
The time has come
获得自由了
to set you free.
弗朗奇身上发生了同样的事情
Hey, hey, the same thing happened to Frankie.
你必须扛过这疼痛
You have to fight through the pain.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
还好
I think so.
炼金术师
来找我
Find me.
我会给你解脱
And I will release you from all of this.
沃利  怎么了
Wally, what is it?
你必须打开门
You have to open the door.
我不能开门  沃利  我不能
I--I can't do that, Wally. I can't.
我会重新使你完整
I can make you whole again.
打开门  我要出去
Open the door! I need to get out!
快点
Now!
闪电侠  就是为你而来
Flash, just who I came to see.
看来你喜欢阴影
So you like shadows?
想试着抓我的影子吗
Want to try and catch mine?
巴里  我们在车里  你能听到吗
Barry, we're in the van. Can you hear us?
我刚像布娃娃一样被扔到地上
And I just got tossed on my ass like a rag doll.
情况不妙
That's not good.
伙计们
All right, guys,
看不到他我什么也做不了
I cannot do anything if I can't see him.
能把这地方照亮吗
Can we light this place up?
光照会减慢他的分子振动
Light's gonna slow down his molecular vibration
这样能抓住他
so we can catch him.
怎么把这地方照亮
How are we gonna light this place up?
-看到这些车了吗  -看到了
- See all these cars? - Yeah.
-我可以黑进车载系统  -然后呢
- I hack into their computers. - Yeah?
-停车场上方的灯  -然后呢
- The park's overhead lights. - Yeah?
用比平克·弗洛伊德演唱会
Blast this guy with more lumens
更强的灯光亮瞎他  -好的
than a Pink Floyd concert. - Yeah.
你干什么
What are you doing?
他需要这个
He's gonna need these.
-她拿的...  -是她拿走了手铐
- She took... - She took the cuffs.
别管了
Okay, just drop it, all right?
巴里  我黑进去了
Barry, I'm in.
好的
Okay.
等我信号
All right, wait until my mark.
信号
And by mark,
指的是
I do mean
我再被打时
next time that I get punched.
这是信号
Mark.
闪电侠
Flash!
不喜欢光吧
Don't like the light, do you?
无处可藏了
Nowhere to hide now.
放我出去
Get me out. Get me out--ah!
救救我
Help me!
拜托  快停下
Please, make it stop.
-爱瑞丝  -沃利  沃利
- Iris! - Hey, Wally, Wally, Wally, look.
没事了  起来
It's over, okay? Come on, come on...
找到我
Find me.
别挡我路
Stay out of my way.
沃利  站住
Wally, stop.
让开
Stay out of my way!
沃利不是他自己了
Wally wasn't himself.
他被附身了
He was possessed.
炼金术师在召唤他
Alchemy was calling for him.
我就知道我不该走的
I knew I shouldn't have left.
没事的  乔  什么都没发生
It's okay, Joe, nothing happened.
他不好  巴里
He's not okay, Barry.
这家伙来缠着他
This thing's coming after him, and--
而我们什么都做不了
and there ain't a damn thing we can do?
我们阻止了阴影
Well, we stopped Shade.
现在我们可以把注意力集中到炼金术师上面
And now we can focus on Alchemy, all right?
除非他送另一个超能力者来袭击中城
Unless he sends another meta to Central City to attack.
那么我们就有麻烦了
Then we're in trouble.
你认为阴影来是为了分散注意力吗
You think Shade was a distraction?
我同意爱瑞丝的看法  我认为对沃利下手
I agree with Iris I think the attack on Wally
和阴影来袭同时发生
and the attack by Shade happened at essentially the same time.
这不是偶然
So that's not a coincidence.
如果是这样  意味着炼金术师要马上送来
If that's true, that means Alchemy's gonna sending
另一个他转化的超能力者
another one of his metas soon.
我们还不确定
We don't know that.
巴里  我们找到了六具外壳
Barry, we found six husks.
所以说除了阴影  磁红女  克拉里斯
So besides Shade, Magenta, and Clariss,
还有三个没找到的
there's still three unaccounted for.
好吧  如果他们要来  我们就阻止他们
Okay, well, if more come, then we'll stop them.
但只要沃利在牢里  炼金术师就无法接近他
But Alchemy can't get Wally if he stays in the cell.
巴里  我们不能就让沃利在里面受苦
Barry, we can't just let Wally suffer in there.
况且  我们什么也不做
And besides, burying our head in the sand
是不能赶走炼金术师的
is not gonna make Alchemy go away.
忽视问题并不能摆脱问题
Ignoring the problem does not get rid of it.
必须要面对
You're gonna have to face it.
是吧
Don't we?
-什么  -没什么
- What? - Nothing.
说吧  凯特琳
Come on, Caitlin.
现在不能说  西斯科
Not right now, Cisco.
我不能一直守着这个秘密
I--just--I can't just keep this in.
你得告诉他们
You have to tell them.
告诉他们什么
Tell them what?
我有超能力
I have powers.
什么
What?
什么超能力
What kind of powers?
冰霜的超能力
The cold kind.
开心了吗
Happy now?
难道我们之间应该互相隐瞒吗
So, what, we're just gonna keep secrets from each other?
这个不是你的秘密
Yeah, well, this wasn't your secret to tell,
好吗  西斯科
was it, Cisco?
我这么做是因为我关心你
I did that because I care about you.
如果你关心我  就会让我
If you cared about me, then you would have
准备好了再告诉他们
let me tell them all when I was ready.
这事发生在我身上  不是你
Because this is happening to me, not you.
变成魔鬼的人是我
I'm the one turning evil.
很快就要离开的人是我
I'm the one who's gonna have to leave soon.
我震波到我们两个在打斗
I vibed the two of us fighting each other in the future.
她是冰霜杀手
She was Killer Frost.
-我去跟她聊聊  -我来
- I'll go talk to her. - I got it.
你知道多久了
How long have you known?
几个月
A few months.
起初我不想接受它发生在我身上的事实
First I didn't want to accept what was happening to me.
然后我不得不接受
And then I had to.
我尝试抑制我的超能力
So then I tried to suppress my powers.
这些超能力无法被抑制
There's no suppressing these powers.
我只是无法相信这是我的人生
I just can't believe that this is my life.
不该发生的
It shouldn't be.
在你们身上发生的事本来都是不会发生的
None of what's happening to any of you should be.
什么意思  我们身上
What do you mean, any of us?
我是说
I mean...
炼金术博士
Dr. Alchemy.
沃利
Wally.
你获得超能力
You getting powers.
甚至丹堤不该在这条时间线死去
Even Dante being dead in this timeline.
全都是因为我创造了闪点
It's all because I created Flashpoint.
还有爱瑞丝  我不知道  我觉得
Even Iris, who, I don't know, I think
她因大家都有超能力她却没有
she's disappointed that she doesn't have powers
而失望
and everyone else does.
不管现在我怎么做
And no matter what I do now,
所有事物都不一样了
everything's different.
以前的时间线没发生过这样的事吗
So none of this happened before?
我很抱歉  凯特琳
I'm sorry, Caitlin.
沃利醒了
Wally's up.
好
Okay.
你感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
我现在不太好
I've been better.
我们该怎么做
What do we do?
我们一定要想办法解决
We got to come up with something.
通过我
Use me.
不行  绝对不行
No. No, no, hell no.
炼金术师召唤我去找他
Alchemy's calling for me to go to him.
跟着我找到他的所在
Follow me wherever he is,
我们就可以阻止他
and we can stop him.
不  我们不会让你这么做
No. We're not asking you to do that.
这是我们阻止他的机会
This is our chance to stop him
我们必须这么做
We have to do it.
沃利
Wally...
爸爸  他要的人是我
Dad, he--he wants me.
他让我痛苦
He's hurting me.
我要反击
So let me fight back.
沃利
Wally?
来找我
Find me.
让他侧躺
Turn him on his side.
好  帮他翻过身  来
All right, get him over, come on.
应该有帮助
This should help.
这是温和的镇静剂
It's a mild sedative.
-这是什么  -氯羟去甲安定
- What is that? - Lorazepam.
给癫痫患者用的
It works on seizures.
不管这是什么希望能有效
Hopefully it'll work on whatever this is.
发作得越来越频繁了
These episodes keep happening more frequently.
这只是暂时的治疗
Yeah, and this is just a temporary fix.
如果不能阻止它  他可能会
If we don't stop it too, he could suffer
永久性脑损伤
from permanent brain damage.
我们别无选择
We don't have a choice.
我们得按沃利说的做  我们得
We have to do what Wally wanted; we have to
通过他找到炼金术师
use him to find Alchemy.
不  我们不能...太危险了
No, we're no-- it's too dangerous.
但什么都不做也很危险
So is doing nothing.
要我提醒大家炼金术博士
Need I remind everyone that Dr. Alchemy
能射出激光  谁知道
has a rock that shoots lasers, so
他还有什么我们不知道的能力吗
who knows what he has up his sleeve?
西斯科说得对
Cisco's right.
万一我们去的是个陷阱呢
What if we're walking into a trap?
你们哪都不会去
You guys aren't walking into anything.
你们都留在这里
You guys are gonna stay here.
如果我们要行动  我们就要做得好
If we're gonna do this, we're gonna do it right.
你在说什么
What does that mean?
我说如果我要让沃利冒险
It means that if I'm gonna put Wally at risk,
我要竭尽所能保护他
I'm gonna use everything in my power to protect him.
复查你们的装备  确保没有遗漏
Double-check your packs. Make sure we have everything.
-准备好了  -好
- Good to go. - Okay.
你有什么计划  警探
So what's the plan, Detective?
这个疯子叫炼金术师
This lunatic, calls himself Alchemy,
在整座城市里出现的外壳
he's the one responsible for all these husks
都跟他有关
we've been finding all over town.
我们相信我们能找到他的位置
But we believe we found a way to get his location.
怎么找
How?
通过他的下一个目标
By using his next target.
你的儿子
Your son?
我们会阻止他的  乔
We'll stop him, Joe.
朱利安在哪里
Where's Julian?
他今天没来
He didn't come in today.
他从来没缺过勤  打给他了吗
What, he never misses a day. You call him?
打了  直接转去语音信箱了
Yeah, it went straight to voicemail.
好吧
Well.
好  各位  开始行动
All right, gents, move out.
出发吧
Let's roll.
好  注意安全
All right, be safe.
我们回头见
We'll see you in a few.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
好了
Yeah.
你记得我说你让我
Hey, you remember when I said that you remind me
想起小时候的我吗
of myself as a kid?
我从来没这么勇敢过
I was never this brave.
他们刚出发
They've just left.
我快好了  我等下就到
I'm almost done. I'll be right there.
西斯科  我为我刚才的行为道歉
Cisco, I am so sorry about how I reacted.
我明白你为什么会告诉大家
I understand why you told everyone.
如果我们彼此隐瞒  对我们是没有帮助的
Never helps when we keep things from each other.
你说得对
You're right.
我很高兴你告诉大家
And I'm glad that you told everyone.
我只是不太会寻求帮助
I'm just not very good at asking for help.
这是遗传我妈的毛病
I get that from my mom.
可是你比你妈妈好多了
You're better than your mother.
我不知道
I don't know.
我挺害怕的  因为她说
I'm just so terrified because she said
如果我一直使用我的超能力
if I keep using my powers, then
我就不可能停下来了
it'll be impossible to stop them.
你妈妈也许是这个地球上
Your mother might be one of the most accomplished
最成功的科学家之一
scientists on this planet,
但在不可能的事上
but when it comes to the impossible,
我们是专家
we're the experts.
我们会帮你的  凯特琳
We're gonna help you, Caitlin.
-好吗  -好
- Okay? - Okay.
我们去帮沃利吧
Let's go help Wally.
好的
You got it.
我们准备进去
We're moving in.
提醒一下  你们进去了
Just remember, once you get in there,
我们是看不到里面的情况的
we're not gonna have eyes
收到
Copy that.
显然这家伙用废弃的地道设立门户
Of course, dude uses an abandoned subway to set up shop.
显然是的
Of course he does.
要找古鲁德的时候他去哪了
Where's Grodd when you need him?
大猩猩古鲁德
Gro--Gorilla Grodd?
你的地球也有有感情的大猩猩吗
You have sentient gorillas on your Earth too?
有啊  还挺多的
Oh, yeah, yeah, we do, many.
挺多的
Many. Yeah.
来找我
Come to me.
华莱士
Wallace.
大家准备就绪吗
Everybody set?
准备好了
We're good.
带路吧
Just lead the way.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
害怕也没关系  沃利
It's okay to be scared, Wally.
我就很害怕
I am.
是吗
You are?
害怕让我保持警惕
Keeps me alert.
那我现在是非常警惕
Then I'm on high alert.
一起干吧
Let's do this.
你好  沃利
Hello, Wally.
是你吗
Are you him?
我脑中听到的声音是你的吗
Are you the voice I've been hearing inside my head?
我是炼金术师
I am Alchemy.
我看见了另一条时间线上的
I've been having visions
自己
of another life.
在那里我速度很快  我是...
Where--where I have speed, where, I'm...
闪电侠
The Flash.
只要你想要
I can give you that back,
我可以让你重新拥有
should you desire it.
我只是想结束这个痛苦
I just want the pain to stop.
会结束的  孩子
It will, child.
不管你想要什么
Whatever you desire,
我都帮你实现
I will see it so.
现在告诉我
Now tell me,
你想重新拥有你被夺走的
do you wish for the life that was taken from you
生活吗
to return?
我想要的是
What I wish for...
你们全部都消失
is all of you gone.
这是个陷阱
It's a trap!
这孩子已经被选中了  闪电侠
The boy has been chosen, Flash.
你不要再阻止必然发生的事
And you will not stand before what must be...
再也不要
Ever again!
不
No!
跪下
Get on your knees!
马上  不许动
Now! Don't move! Don't move!
不许动  跪下
Get down!
跪在地上
On the ground.
我让你跪在地上
I said get on the ground.
这是个重大的错误
That was a grave mistake.
-你还好吗  -我会好的
- You okay? - I'll be fine.
沃利
Wally?
没事
Yeah.
结束了  炼金术师
It's over, Alchemy.
结束了
Over?
你不知道
You have no idea
什么要开始了
what's about to begin.
怎么回事
What the hell?
你们看见了吗
Did you guys see that?
看见什么
See what?
快走  快离开这里
Go. Get the hell out of here!
沃利  快到门口去  跟紧我
Wally, move towards the door! Stick with me!
走另外一边  走另外一边  快走快走
The other way! The other way! Go! Go! Go! Go!
沃利  快走
Wally, go!
你没事吧
You all right?
华莱士
Wallace.
华莱士·韦斯特
Wallace West.
获取你的超能力
Take your power.
沃利
Wally.
沃利  不要
Wally, don't!
沃利
Wally!
你是谁
Who are you?
萨维塔
Savitar.
极速之神
The God of Speed.